# Leandro Loiácono

# web dev experience & work



Portfolio web design with JS, React, Styled Components.

Project 'Travelwith'

Web-app for organize travel with friends (JS, React, SCSS, MongoDB)

Project 'localSHOP://'

Web for local small business (JS, React, SCSS, MongoDB)

Project 'CalendarApp'

Project for sharing events with an small group of people (JS, React, Redux)

Project 'JournalApp'

<u>An small project web-app to keep a small journal (JS, React, Redux)</u>

### experience

**Teacher Assistant** 

IRONHACK Sept 2020 - Dec 2020

Teacher Assistant for the WebDev. Bootcamp.

**Content Moderator** 

Majorel May 2019 - Jun 2020

Content analysis and moderation for one of the biggest social media companies worldwide.

**Customer service Supervisor** 

Hospital Aleman Services Apr 2012 - Dec 2018

Coordinate and train a team of agents of customer services for a health care insurance company.

#### education

**Full Stack Developer Bootcamp** 

Ironhack Jun 2020 - Sept 2020

**Professional Photographer** 

Escuela Fotografía Andy Goldstein Feb 2017 - Nov 2018



#### contact

leandro.a.loiacono@gmail.com

Tel: +34 693 004488

LinkedIn: @leandro-loiacono/

Github: @leanloia

#### bio

My professional path started in Argentina, where I worked in the Customer Services Industry for some years and, in parallel, dedicate my free time to get more involved in other areas, such as Programming, Photography and learning new languages.

In the beginning of 2019, I decided to move to Barcelona, and change my professional and personal life almost completely. I decided to make a career change and I joined a Full Stack WebDev Bootcamp at Ironhack, and currently I'm starting a new path in a new Industry, which fills me with excitement and push me forward to a new self-development path.

## skills & expertise

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- Redux
- Express.js
- HTML & CSS
- React.js
- Spanish (native)
- English (advanced)
- Catalan (intermediate)
- German (begginer)